you have a Band-Aid who exactly do you
think I am someone who carries Band-Aids
huh guess
not hey there Moira how have you been
busier than you I'd assume I missed you
too you look great by the way same
saccharine tongue same empty head you
stopping in to see Max I love how you
make him squirm it's amusing I don't
even experiment on omnex yet
yet I'd rather wait a century for
Progress than cause the harm you have
what a joy it must be to feel entitled
to
patience I could have rebuilt you
without all that metal and left me a
monster like other creations that is a
matter of
perspective you're the one making
Abominations H as the strongest woman in
the world
you must see Merit in pushing Humanity's
limits all I see is a fool mistaking a
strong body for a gullible mind don't
die on me now you're one of my finest
experiments flattery will get you the
grave you are remembering to take your
supplements look at these guns and ask
me
again does it bother you that you've
taken as many lives as you've saved I
don't mind killing monsters
but go on keep pushing me what is your
fascination with artificial Decay well
to reverse entropy we must tame it but
inflicting it on yourself you're
withering away I've always thrived under
a
deadline have you enjoyed your time away
with the fairies Dr deer they do make
lovely
conversation anyone want to hear my
favorite joke about the periodic table
nah
what a nauseating boat of deja vu yep
working with you has always made me sick
are you planning to whine the whole time
[Music]
again don't you ever feel remorse for
the pain you have caused pain makes one
stronger you should know that better
than
anyone you looking for a lab assistant
I'm great with chemicals certainly we
would be get by testing your tolerance
for pain what's pain have to do with
science everything My Strange little
friend you've been rather quiet today
doctor I've gotten a lot done can a fish
that never sees the surface no it's
underwater I wonder if frogs dream of
ponds if one built a violin of plank
length could one play music into another
Universe someone must build a particle
collider around the
Sun there it
goes you look
cheery as cheery as you are
significant this foolish mission is
taking time away from my experiments
aande think of it as
fieldwork you're a geneticist if you're
up for it I bet our bioarchaeology team
would love to have you the dad tell
intriguing Tales but my interest lies
with the living
so sweet Adena has grown into a
domineering Beast my name is Ora you
would be wise to remember it aggression
is no substitute for Ability reckon
that's true good thing I have
both I've read about the genetic therapy
they put you through it sounds
unpleasant it was but ignorance was
worse don't bother reason is lost on
her Dr Lea was not fond of you was she
any F of you of course I was her life's
work it seemed to me she was far more
taken with your
predecessor how are you funding your
crimes against humanity these days my
old friend's Innovation and
Imagination a shame you've never met
them what are you up to Moira wouldn't
you like to know fine I'll hack you
later
you have an intense gaze doctor I'm
thinking on how best to utilize you in
the coming battle you mean
perhaps I have yet to see a report on
your latest experiment it's making
progress our timeline is non-negotiable
keep interrupting me surely that'll
expedite things so I'm trying to ask
everybody this what is your favorite
animal scolopendra gigantia uh yeah I
can see it is there nothing you can do
for this pain think of it as fuel
beneath the Flames of your
[Music]
Vengeance you and hiy need to stop
frying sigma's brain I'm trying to help
your little friend and yourself yes
let's discuss morality and hypocrisy
while we're at
it I have heard of your
experiments there is no honor in what
you do shimar where do I know that name
from oh that's right the family of
criminals healing and hurting H I guess
we're not that
different I assure you we are nothing
alike in the field doctor testing a
hypothesis perhaps with the rate at
which our colleagues get injured I
expect I'll be testing my
patience these carpal tunnels slowing
down my wpm I can fix it
and more uh how about just taping it up
buffers on the
table can one know that one knows
nothing can a single grain of sand
differentiate between Heap and not heap
if the universe is a simulation why
aren't there more elephant seals it
Thrills me to put aside my preparations
and humor your brilliant inquiries
doctor it Thrills me kind words thanks
you I've read your report on
cryogenically preserving severed
appendages I'd be happy to resist in
your research no thank you I don't think
our methodologies are very aligned of
course I've heard you prefer working
alone come now doctor I was only hoping
to lend a
hand how fair is your research Dr zegler
making much progress through all that
red tape it's called the hypocritic oath
doctor ring any
beds easily how can you experiment on
those cute little
rabbits if you know what you're looking
for inquiry is unnecessary but if you
don't know how do you
inquire somehow even more tiresome than
the Chicken and the
Egg are you breathing petrol or
something more interesting what some no
thank you I'll just
observe Moira I should crush you like a
bug for what you've done did you know
that certain centipedes kill prey 15
times their size what are you saying I'm
advising my prey not to test me you've
been distant lately laor by your design
pondering anything
unusual dangerous no never you ever
broken patient confidentiality I can't
say you're good
there is always room for Brilliance at
Oasis I'm honored but I have some
reservations about your oh what's the
word atrocities
inhumanity crimes against nature huh any
of those will do our foes make such a
nuisance of themselves is that an
emotion I detect laqua